Guide to the Alan Pryce-Jones Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, [ca.1914]-96; Series II; 6.5; (16 boxes)
  - ESSAYS, LECTURES, AND RADIO APPEARANCES
    - "Europe and the Returning Soldier," draft, typescript (Box 33, Folder 1587)
    - "First Meeting: Reg Butler, Sculptor, and Alan Pryce-Jones [...]," transcript of BBC broadcast, 1959 Apr 27 (Box 33, Folder 1588)
    - "Fourth of June Notebook," draft, typescript, corrected, [1949] (Box 33, Folder 1589)
    - "Freedom of the Imagination"
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1590)
      - Draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1591)
      - Draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1592)
      - Setting copy, typescript, with summary of discussion following lecture, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1593)
    - "The Glories of Glass," proof and printed version, House and Garden, 1963 May (Box 33, Folder 1594)
      See also: Oversize, Box 65, Folder 2419
    - "Goethe in the Modern World," script for BBC broadcast, typescript carbon, corrected, 1948 Jan 4 (Box 33, Folder 1595)
    - "Goethe's Lyrics," script for broadcast, typescript mimeograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1596)
    - "The Good Life"
      - Scripts for three BBC broadcasts, typescript, corrected, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 1597)
      - Printed version, The Listener, with fourth related essay, "Virtue in Our Time", 1953 (Box 33, Folder 1598)
      - "Virtue in Our Time," proof, [1953]
        See: Oversize, Box 65, Folder 2420
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 1599)
    - "Gustave Flaubert," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1600)
    - "Hawthorne in England"
      See: notebook, Box 35, folder 1690
    - "Helen Stanley" ("Favourite Characters")
      - Draft of narration, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1601)
      - Script for BBC broadcast, typescript mimeograph, 1959 Aug 26 (Box 33, Folder 1602)
    - "The House on John Street," printed version, House & Garden, September issue, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1603)
    - "How to Act Like a Writer in London and New York," draft, typescript photocopy, corrected, & printed version (Box 34, Folder 1604)
    - "The Idea of a Provincial Theatre," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1605)
    - The Immigrant Experience, contract for contribution to, 1971 Mar 4 (Box 34, Folder 1606)
    - "The Importance of Being Brecht," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1607)
    - "Is a National Theatre Necessary?", galley proof, London Magazine (Box 34, Folder 1608)
    - "Ist der Roman tot?" printed version, Neue Zürcher Zeitung, 1954 Sep 19 (Box 34, Folder 1609)
    - "Late Transplant: Why I Left London for New York," printed version, Harpers' Magazine, August issue, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 1610)
    - "Laxenburg," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1611)
    - "Lecture," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1612)
      Accompanied by a manuscript
      titled "Marianne," and two
      printed pages from a preface
      to T. S. Eliot's poetry
    - The Life of Ludwig van Beethoven, by Alexander W. Thayer, proof of APJ's introduction to, corrected, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 1613)
    - "La littérature anglaise," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1614)
    - "La littérature moderne ne fait-elle pas une trop grande place à la confession?", typescript, corrected, 1953 Dec 1 (Box 34, Folder 1615)
      Transcript of or script for a
      conversation between APJ,
      B. De Monvel, and Amrouche
    - "A London Likeness," BBC broadcast script, typescript, corrected, 1968 Jun 26 (Box 34, Folder 1616)
    - "The Mind of George Meredith," draft, typescript, corrected (Box 34, Folder 1617)
      Accompanied by holograph
      notes, "Trevelyan on Meredith"
    - "Modern English Literature," incomplete draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1618)
    - "The Modern English Novel," draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1619)
    - "A Modern Prophet," [Aldous Huxley], draft, typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1620)
    - "Moderne englische Literatur," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1621)
    - "Month in New York" series
      - "August in New York," script for BBC broadcast, typescript, corrected, 1967 Aug 8 (Box 34, Folder 1622)
      - [September?] in New York," incomplete draft, typescript carbon, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1623)
      - "April in New York," script for BBC broadcast, typescript mimeograph, 1968 Apr 28 (Box 34, Folder 1624)
      - "March in New York," script for BBC broadcast, typescript mimeograph, 1968 Mar 24 (Box 34, Folder 1625)
      - "November in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1968] (Box 34, Folder 1626)
      - "January in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and two BBC broadcast scripts, typescript carbon, 1969 Jan 27 (Box 34, Folder 1627)
      - "February in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, BBC broadcast scripts, and printed, The Listener, 1969 Feb 27 (Box 34, Folder 1628)
      - "April in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and BBC broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1969 Apr 21 (Box 34, Folder 1629)
      - "May in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and BBC broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1969 May 27 (Box 34, Folder 1630)
      - "June in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and BBC broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1969 Jun 23 (Box 34, Folder 1631)
        the BBC, 1969 Jul 30
      - "September in New York," photocopy of corrected typescript draft, [1969] (Box 34, Folder 1632)
      - "October in New York," photocopy of corrected typescript draft, [1969] (Box 34, Folder 1633)
      - "November in New York," photocopy of corrected typescript draft, [1969] (Box 34, Folder 1634)
      - "December in New York," photocopy of corrected typescript draft, [1969] (Box 34, Folder 1635)
      - "January in New York," photocopy of corrected typescript draft, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1636)
      - "February in New York," draft, typecript, corrected, and audience survey summary, typescript carbon, 1971 Feb 26 (Box 34, Folder 1637)
      - "March in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1638)
      - "April in New York," photocopy of corrected typescript draft, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1639)
      - "May in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1640)
      - "June in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and photocopy, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1641)
      - "September in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and photocopy, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1642)
      - "November in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1643)
      - "December in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1970] (Box 34, Folder 1644)
      - "February in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and photocopy, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1645)
      - "March in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, photocopy, and printed version, The Listener, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1646)
      - "April in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1647)
      - "May in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1648)
      - "June in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1649)
      - "September in New York," draft typescript, corrected, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1650)
      - "October in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and printed excerpt, The Listener, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1651)
      - "November in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and photocopy, [1971] (Box 34, Folder 1652)
      - "December in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, photocopy, and BBC broadcast script, mimeograph, 1971 Dec 31 (Box 34, Folder 1653)
      - "January in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and photocopy, corrected, [1972] (Box 34, Folder 1654)
      - "March in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, with holograph addition, [1972] (Box 34, Folder 1655)
      - "September in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, and photocopy, [1972] (Box 34, Folder 1656)
      - "October in New York," draft, typescript, corrected, [1972] (Box 34, Folder 1657)
    - "Music and Modern Poetry"
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1658)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1659)
    - "Newport," draft, typescript photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1660)
    - "Newport, Rhode Island"
      - Draft, typescript photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1661)
      - Galley proof, 1973 Mar 5
      - Printed version, The Listener, 1973 Mar 22 (Box 35, Folder 1662)
    - "Notes for a Portrait: Houston Stewart Chamberlain," typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1663)
      Accompanied by typescript notes on Lebenswege meines Denkens.
      See also: "The Wandering Aryan," Box 35, folder 1686
      See also: notebook, Box 35, folder 1690
    - "Nothing Can Erase Christmas," proof, House and Garden, December issue, 1964
    - "The Novel"
    - "On Kafka," draft, typescript, corrected, 1959 Nov 3 (Box 35, Folder 1664)
    - "On Not Speaking the Truth," essay outline submitted to Curtis Brown, Ltd., typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1665)
    - "Persoenliches Bekenntnis," draft, typescript, corrected, 1957 Apr 8 (Box 35, Folder 1666)
    - "La poesie anglaise d'aujourd'hui," draft, typescript mimeograph, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1667)
    - "Preface" [to Goethe?], draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1668)
    - "A Program of Poems by Edith Sitwell," contract to write the liner notes for, 1955 Jun 19 (Box 35, Folder 1669)
    - "Prosper Mérimée," script for BBC broadcast, typescript carbon, 1947 Nov 11 (Box 35, Folder 1670)
    - "René Bouché," biographical sketch, printed, exhibition catalogue, Newport Art Association and Museum, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1671)
    - "The Rococo Spirit," galley proofs, The Spoken Word, n.d.
    - "Der Rosenkavalier," contract for booklet on, 1947 Jun 23 (Box 35, Folder 1672)
    - "Sainte-Beuve: The Critic as Moralist," draft, typescript, corrected, and printed version, The Listener, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 1673)
    - "The Secret Attraction," photocopy of article printed in The Times Literary Supplement, 1955 Feb 25 (Box 35, Folder 1674)
      Annotated on the original,
      "by Allen Pryce-Jones, Author?"
    - "The Serious American," printed version, The Listener, 1963 Jan 10 (Box 35, Folder 1675)
    - "Slovakia: the Springboard?", draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1676)
    - "Small Wonders for Small Plunder," printed version (Box 35, Folder 1677)
    - "The State of Civilisation in France," printed version, The Listener, 1954 Dec 30 (Box 35, Folder 1678)
    - "The Theatre in Great Britain," BBC broadcast script, typescript mimeograph, 1960 Feb 4 (Box 35, Folder 1679)
      See also: "Is a National Theatre Necessary?", Box 34, folder 1608
    - "This I Believe," BBC broadcast script, typescript mimeograph, 1953 Jan 26 (Box 35, Folder 1680)
    - "Translation and the Americans," printed version, The Times Literary Supplement, 1970 Sep 25 (Box 35, Folder 1681)
    - "The Unbroken 'Ring'," printed version, The Listener, 1953 Oct 29 (Box 35, Folder 1682)
    - "Unseen Art," BBC broadcast script, typescript mimeograph, 1971 Feb 10 (Box 35, Folder 1683)
    - "Vienna"
    - "Viewpoint," column in The Times Literary Supplement, proofs and printed versions, 1972-74 (Box 35, Folder 1684)
    - "Vladimir Nabokov," proof, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1685)
    - "The Wandering Aryan: Houston Stewart Chamberlain," draft, typescript, corrected, [1953] (Box 35, Folder 1686)
      See also: "Notes for a Portrait," Box 35, folder 1663
    - "While We Were Driving to Georgia," printed version [unidentified publication], n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1687)
    - Young Törless by Robert Musil, contract & setting typescript of APJ's preface to, photocopy, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1688)
      APJ's preface to the [1955?] English translation, for inclusion in Gale anthology Twentieth-Century Literary Criticism.
    - Notebook of holograph drafts, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1689)
      Contains essays "The Novel," "The Creative Spirit of the 1920s," "Vienna," and other drafts; also contains reviews of E. M. Forster's "Billy Budd" libretto, a work of André Gide, and other drafts.
    - Notebook of holograph drafts, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1690)
      Contains essays "Hawthorne in England," "Houston Stewart Chamberlain," and other drafts; also contains the story "The Tulips" ("An Evening"), and drafts of reviews.
    - Untitled Drafts and Fragments
      - "Every age has its own literary character [...]," typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1691)
      - [On the importance of evil in modern literature], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1692)
      - [On the Ford Foundation's support of opera], typescript carbon, corrected (Box 35, Folder 1693)
      - [On Galveston, Texas], typescript, corrected, and photocopy (Box 35, Folder 1694)
      - "Je ne prétends pas prendre la parole en philosophe [...]," typescript, corrected (Box 35, Folder 1695)
      - [On literary criticism], in French, incomplete typescript mimeograph, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1696)
      - [On literary periodicals], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1697)
      - [On Newport], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1698)
      - [On Newport], incomplete typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1699)
      - [On politics], holograph draft, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1700)
      - "Quelles sont les raisons qui vous ont amené à la carrière des lettres?" [...], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1701)
      - [On Mr. and Mrs. John Hay Whitney as collectors], typescript carbon, corrected, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1702)
      - [On Wagner], typescript, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1703)
      - [On drama criticism], fragment, typescript photocopy (Box 35, Folder 1704)
      - [On New York], fragment, typescript, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1705)
      - [On St. Patrick's Day], fragment, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1706)
    - Notes
      - "Contemporary English Literature," [and on T. S. Eliot], holograph and typescript (Box 35, Folder 1707)
      - "Thoughts in an airport bookstore," typescript, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1708)
      - "Why Write an A.?", holograph, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1709)
      - [On architects], holograph, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1710)
      - [On Samuel Pepys and later diarists], typescript, [1954?] (Box 35, Folder 1711)
      - [On Erasmus Darwin], holograph, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1712)
      - [On Laforgue and Lautreamont], typescript (Box 35, Folder 1713)
      - [Comparing literary culture in Great Britain and the United States], holograph and typescript (Box 35, Folder 1714)
      - [On French literature], n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1715)
      - [On literature, beginning with Henry Adams], holograph and typescript (Box 35, Folder 1716)
      - "What one read when I was young," holograph and typescript (Box 35, Folder 1717)
      - "Myself, Sand, Sea, Sun," holograph (Box 35, Folder 1718)
      - [On literature], general, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1719)
      - [On Meidling and the Springer family] (Box 35, Folder 1720)
    - Related Material
      - Itinerary and notes, Scandinavian lecture tour (Box 35, Folder 1721)
      - Itineraries, notes, and vaccination certificate, Japanese lecture tour, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1722)
        Accompanied by biographical
        information about members of
        a "Japanese Theatre Group"
        who visited New York prior
        to APJ's trip to Japan
      - Contracts for speaking engagements: Savage & Consolini and University Speakers Bureau, 1963-65 (Box 35, Folder 1723)
      - Lecture announcements and page from University Speaker's Bureau booklet, 1959-67, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1724)
      - Lecture reviews and notices, 1955-64, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1725)
  - REVIEWS
    - Review Columns and Regular Assignments
      - British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC)
        Arranged alphabetically by author
        of work reviewed
        - Roger Fulford, The Prince Consort, broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1949 Mar 26 (Box 36, Folder 1726)
          See also: notebook above, Box 38, folder 1785
        - Graham Greene, The Quiet American, broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1955 Dec 15 (Box 36, Folder 1727)
        - Erich Heller, The Ironic German: a Study of Thomas Mann, broadcast scripts, English and German, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 1728)
        - Hans Keyser, Harmonia Plantarum, broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 1729)
        - Arthur Koestler, Arrow in the Blue, broadcast script, typescript mimeograph, corrected (incomplete), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1730)
        - Raymond Las Vergnas, L'angleterre change de cap, broadcast script, typescript mimeograph, corrected, 1957 May 2 (Box 36, Folder 1731)
        - Percy Lubbock, Portrait of Edith Wharton, draft, typescript, corrected, & broadcast script, typescript carbon, 1947 Oct 21 (Box 36, Folder 1732)
        - "Weekly Book Summary no. 497," on Kathleen Nott and Stephen Spender, draft, typescript mimeograph, [1954] (Box 36, Folder 1733)
        - " The New Yorker at 50," printed version, The Listener, 1975 Feb 27 (Box 36, Folder 1734)
          Also in this issue: David
          Pryce-Jones television review
        - "The Theatre of Edward Albee," printed version, The Listener, 1966 Nov 24 (Box 36, Folder 1735)
        - "A Road with No Turning: on the Beat Generation printed version, The Listener, 1958 Jul 3 (Box 36, Folder 1736)
        - "The Messiahs of the Milk Bars?", on Declaration, printed version, The Listener, 1957 Nov 7 (Box 36, Folder 1737)
        - Other short reviews, printed, The Listener, 1930-51 (Box 36, Folder 1738)
      - The Chicago Sun-Times
        - Printed reviews, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1739)
      - Commonweal
        - Printed reviews, 1964-68 (Box 36, Folder 1740)
      - London Magazine
        - Printed reviews, [1954-58] (Box 36, Folder 1741)
      - The London Mercury
        - Bound volumes containing APJ's printed writings in the Mercury (chiefly reviews, but also poems, stories, and essays), 1928-33 (Box 36, Folder 1742-1743)
          Poems include:
          "Silence after Music"
          "London Siren"
          "Letter to a Friend"
          "Our Lady at the Manger"
          "The Old General"
          "Recollection of Windsor"
          "Any Young Poet is Speaking"
          "Conventional Poem")
          Stories include:
          "Early February"
          "The Country House"
          Essays include:
          "Erasmus Darwin"
          "Museum Piece"
          "Kenneth Grahame"
      - The New York Herald Tribune
        - "Daily Book Review" and "Book Week," printed reviews, 1957-66 (Box 36, Folder 1744-1748)
        - "Daily Book Review" and "Book Week," printed reviews, 1957-66 (Box 37, Folder 1749-1750)
      - The New York Review
        - Printed reviews, 1966-86 (Box 37, Folder 1751)
      - [ The New York Times ?]
        - "The Literary Scene," printed reviews, [1968-69], n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1752)
      - The New York Times Book Review
        - Printed reviews, 1966-68 (Box 37, Folder 1753)
          See also: Series I, Correspondence, New York Times, Box 16, folder 880
      - The Oakland Tribune, "Book Mark"
        - Printed reviews, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1754)
      - The Observer
        - "At the Theatre," printed reviews in scrapbook, 1959-60 (Box 37, Folder 1755)
        - Other printed reviews, [1981] (Box 37, Folder 1756)
      - The Sunday Telegraph
        - Printed reviews, 1967-69 (Box 37, Folder 1757)
      - Theatre Arts
        - Issues containing APJ's reviews, 1960-64 (Box 37a, Folder 1758-1762)
        - Issues containing APJ's reviews, 1960-64 (Box 38, Folder 1763-1764)
      - The Times (London)
        - "Talking of Books," printed reviews, 1959-61 (Box 38, Folder 1765)
        - Other printed reviews, 1953-54 (Box 38, Folder 1766)
      - The Times Literary Supplement
        - Printed reviews, 1946-85 (Box 38, Folder 1767)
      - The Washington Post
        - "Book World," printed reviews, 1967-[81], n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1768)
      - The World Journal Tribune
        - "World of Books," "Book Day," and "Book Week," printed reviews, 1966-67 (Box 38, Folder 1769)
    - Other Reviews
      - Drafts
        of work reviewed, with the exception
        of one notebook filed at end of group
        - Nicholas Barker, Stanley Morrison, draft, typescript, corrected, and printed version, [1972] (Box 38, Folder 1770)
        - Quentin Bell, Virginia Woolf: a Biography, draft, typescript, corrected [fragment], [1972] (Box 38, Folder 1771)
        - John Berryman [?], typescript carbon [fragment], n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1772)
        - Alistair Cooke, "series on American history," draft, typescript, corrected, [ca. 1976] (Box 38, Folder 1773)
        - Barbara Goldsmith, Little Gloria, draft, typescript, corrected, [1980] (Box 38, Folder 1774)
        - Lillian Hellman, An Unfinished Woman, draft, typescript carbon and printed version, [1969] (Box 38, Folder 1775)
        - Barbara Heyman, Samuel Barber, draft, typescript carbon, corrected, and proof, corrected, [1992] (Box 38, Folder 1776)
        - James King, The Last Modern: A Life of Herbert Read, draft, typescript, corrected, [1990] (Box 38, Folder 1777)
        - Marie Jacqueline Lancaster, Brian Howard: Portrait of a Failure, draft, typescript carbon, [1968] (Box 38, Folder 1778)
        - Arthur Miller, The Creation of the World and Other Business, draft, typescript, corrected, [ca. 1973] (Box 38, Folder 1779)
        - Emily Post's Etiquette, photocopy of corrected typescript draft, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1780)
        - Sally Bedell Smith, Reflected Glory: the Life of Pamela Churchill Harriman, draft, typescript, corrected, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 1781)
        - Robert Speaight, The Life of Hilaire Belloc, draft, typescript, corrected, [1957] (Box 38, Folder 1782)
        - Tom Stoppard, Lord Malquist and Mr. Moon, draft, typescript carbon [fragment], [1968] (Box 38, Folder 1783)
        - Untitled review of various theater productions in New York, draft, typescript, corrected, [1963] (Box 38, Folder 1784)
        - Notebook of holograph drafts, [1949-50], n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1785)
          Contains reviews of:
          Roger Fulford, The Prince Consort
          Virginia Woolf, The Captain's Death Bed and Other Essays
          Karl Jaspers, Die Schuldfrage
          Robert S. Hitchens, The Green Carnation
          Osbert Sitwell, Left Hand, Right Hand
          and the diaries of Kafka, Novalis,
          and Ramuz, among other reviews
          also contains essays on Aldous
          Huxley, Wordsworth, "The 1549
          Prayer Book", and "Lettre de
          Londres"
      - Clippings and proofs
        - Single reviews, printed versions, various publications, 1938-95 (Box 38, Folder 1786)
          Includes reviews of:
          Aczel, Tamas, Ten Years After
          Amis, Kingsley, I Want it Now
          APA-Phoenix [repertory theatre],
          1967 season
          Andric, Ivo, The Pasha's Concubine
          Betjeman, John, A Nip in the Air
          Burke, John, and Colin Caldwell, Hogarth: The Complete Engravings
          Downing, Antoinette and Vincent Scully, The Architectural Heritage of Newport, Rhode Island
          Gathorne-Hardy, Robert, ed., Ottoline: the Early Memoirs of Lady Ottoline Morrell
          Greene, Graham, [novels]
          Hemisfair '68 [fair in San Antonio, TX]
          Isham, Heyward, Remaking Russia
          Lewis, Robert, Michel, Michel
          Murdoch, Iris, The Nice and the Good
          Potter, Beatrix, The Journals of Beatrix Potter
          Newport Music Festival [1971]
          Sitwell, Sacheverell, An Indian Summer
          Wicks, Margaret C. W., The Italian Exiles in London